Zenia Gist

Phone: 918.640.7967 | Email: zeniagist@gmail.com | Portfolio: zeniagist.github.io

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Experienced coding bootcamp graduate with extensive background with developing mobile applications, and building websites from the ground up using JavaScript, React, and Angular. Professional strengths include creative problemsolving, written and verbal communication, and time management. Detail-oriented mindset from 5+ years of experience in the finance industry.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, SQL, HTML, CSS,

Database: MySQL, MongoDB

ISON

Frameworks and Libraries: React, React Native,

Other: Heroku, Git, Bash, Microsoft Office Suite

Angular, Express, Bootstrap, jQuery

FEATURED PROJECTS

Event Meetup - Live Demo | GitHub Repo

Serverless PWA using Google Calendar API to fetch upcoming events

- Hosted by a serverless function with AWS using the test-driven development (TDD) approach. Users can search for a city and view a list of events hosted in the selected city.
- Tech Specs: React, NodeJS, Gherkin, Google Calendar API, AWS (online server), HTML5, CSS

filmFlix - Live Demo | GitHub Repo

Full-stack web movie database app which provides access to info about movies in the database

- Provides users with the access to information about different movies, directors and genres. Users are able to sign up, update personal information, and create a list of their favorite movies.
- Tech Specs: Angular, TypeScript, Node.JS, Express, MongoDB, Passport, HTML5, CSS

Chatterbox - Live Demo on Andriod Emulator | GitHub Repo

Native mobile chat app that allows users to send pictures and location

- The chat interface functionality is created with the Gifted Chat library are stored locally with Google Firestore Database and Google Firebase authentication.
- Users can send messages, images, and location data both online and offline
- Tech Specs: React Native, Firebase, Expo, Gifted Chat, Android Studio, HTML5, CSS

WORK EXPERIENCE

HIRECALL/TRAK-1 TECHNOLOGY (Temporary Staffing Agency) -- Tulsa, OK

Accounting/Payroll Specialist,

July 2020 to Present (*Returned at company's request due to previous stellar performance*) January 2016 to June 2018

- Processed and managed the timeliness and accuracy for a national background screening company with multiple locations. Reconciled, closed, and validated monthly sub-ledger while resolving all issues.
- Facilitated company's return budget by meeting with department heads to understand the best method to receive budget reports to fit their needs. The result was the increased use of reports and faster decision-making attention variances

PEOPLEFACTS (Background Screening firm providing background reports) -- Tulsa, OK

Outbound Client Engagement Specialist,

June 2018 to July 2020

- Quality check of all criminal background screens for accuracy and turnaround time. Identified criminal searches which were past the county or state determined turnaround time and investigated the reasoning
- Displayed and achieved solid communication when providing important updates on delayed and closed courts to the criminal research team

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development

June 2021

CAREERFOUNDRY-- ONLINE BOOTCAMP

AS in Computer Information Systems TULSA COMMUNITY COLLEGE -- Tulsa, OK

May 2020